Today imagining a website without any images and media is very hard to do.
在当今时代 很难想象会有一个 一点图片和多媒体都没有的网站
But when you think back about when websites were first designed,
但当你回想网站开发的最初阶段
they were purely content, text content.
你会发现其实那时操作的 只是一些纯文本内容
But of course today you can't envision a YouTube without the videos or
当然了 既然我们进入了 21 世纪 一个没有视频的 YouTube 和没有图像的 Pinterest
a Pinterest without the images.
就变得很难想象了
So, images and media add enormous value to web sites these days.
"总之 图像和多媒体的价值无与伦比"
You were expecting me to say that, weren't you?
咳 你是不是在想我会这么说 ?
Well, not quite.
不过，也不一定
This is what I was planning to say.
这才是我想说的
A picture is worth $12 on iStockPhoto.com.
毕竟在 iStockPhoto.com 上 一张图片只值 12 美金
Okay, enough with those corny jokes.
咳 我想你也受不了这个平淡陈旧的玩笑 让我们就此打住吧
Let's move on to talking about images and media and how to include them on websites.
接下来让我们学习如何将图像和多媒体 加进我们的网站中
Paying a quick visit to your course website yourself, you can
首先看一下我们的课程网页的
now begin to look for images and media that are already included in this website.
图像和多媒体
Now, you can easily see that we have a logo up there, which obviously didn't
你应该可以发现这里有个 logo
get there without an image being included into the website design.
显然没有图像的话 这部分就不是长这样的了
And obviously you see those pictures there, images all over again.
然后这里也有一堆图像
Go into your course content and there you have, video on your website.
当你访问课程内容时 你可以看到一些视频
So, anywhere you turn you can't run away from images and
总之 图像和多媒体
media and their use on websites.
几乎是无处不在的
Let's now talk in particular about Bootstraps classes to support images.
接着 让我们学习一些 支持图像的 Bootstrap 类
Now when you include images on your website,
当你想在你的网站中加入图像时
you would of course use the img tag there.
你需要用 img 标签
Now inside the img tag you will supply the source as an attribute.
然后对这个 img 标签 你需要设置它的 src 属性
The class that you can use for images
某些支持图像的 Bootstrap 类
using Bootstrap classes to make the images responsive,
可以让图像变成响应式图像
you would specify them as img-responsive.
你只要设置 class="img-responsive" 就行
This way your image will automatically adapt as the website
响应式图像 正如其名 能够自动地
is viewed on different screens.
适应各种不同大小的屏幕
The image will automatically adapt itself to the size of the parent element,
详细地说 就是这个图像会根据其 上一层 HTML 元素的大小
and appropriately, will display on the screen.
来恰当地显示在用户的屏幕上
Now, you can also use additional classes to control
然后就是 你能加进一些额外的类
the shape in which the image is being displayed on the screen.
来定制这个图像的更多属性
You can use image rounded circle and thumbnail.
比如说 img-rounded, img-circle 还有 img-thumbnail 之类的
Rounded will put rounded corners to your image,
img-rounded 会让你图像的四个角 变成四段圆弧
circle will obviously display your image inside a circle.
至于 img-circle 则会把你的图像 放进一个圆圈内
And thumbnail would add some borders to your image.
img-thumbnail 则会在你的图像四周 加上一些边框
I wonder who that is?
你可能还是不太懂它们具体长啥样
In the example, you can see me using image rounded, image circle and
所以我在这里提供了栗子 从左到右依次是
image thumbnail on the image being displayed there.
img-rounded, img-circle 和 img-thumbnail
This is the result of using the image classes in Bootstrap.
相信这三个栗子能让你更好地明白 这三个类该用在什么场合
Another interesting class in Bootstrap is the thumbnail class.
另外一个有趣的 Bootstrap 类 就是 thumbnail 类
In a thumbnail class, as you can see from the code there,
使用它的一个栗子的代码 我已经贴在这里了
you would surround the content In a div with the class thumbnail.
它是通过一个 div 来实现的
Now inside the thumbnail, you will specify your image, and
在这个 div 的下面 你可以指定一个图像
in addition to the image, you can also specify a caption for the image.
然后就是 你可以为这个图像提供一段说明
If you don't include the caption,
如果你没有提供的话
then it'll be displayed like a thumbnail on this grid.
那么就只是一个单纯的图像而已
Now the thumbnail class is very useful for
这个 thumbnail 类是很有用的
creating a gallery of images on your webpage.
如果你想在你的网页上放一系列的图像的话 它将会提供一个清晰而优雅的排版
If you want to you can also include additional caption to your image.
特别是如果你还想为你的图像放一段说明的话 用 thumbnail 类是不错的选择
In this example, you see me using the caption to include
在这个栗子里 你可以看到我放了一段说明
some additional information together with the image there.
来解释这张图像是什么
Another class that you can use to display images in media,
另外一个你能拿来显示图像的类是 media
is the media-object class.
或称其多媒体对象亦可
To use the media-object class you would enclose everything inside a media div.
为了实现一个多媒体对象 你需要在最外层放一个 div
And inside the media div you would have two inner divs.
这个 div 要设置 "class=media"
One with the media-left or the media-right option.
然后在这个 div 下面通常有两个 div
And the second one with the media-body.
一个会设置 class="media-left" 或 "media-right" 另一个则会设置 class="media-body"
Now, the display of the content will be as shown in the example to the right.
然后使用多媒体对象的效果 则如右图所示
The image will be displayed as a thumbnail or whichever way you choose
你会发现图像和之前 thumbnail 的一样 当然你也可以定制成其它样式
to on the left side, and on the right side the actual content will be displayed.
然后大格局是图像在左内容在右
The media-object class is very useful to construct
多媒体对象同样是一个很有用的
a list of items together with a thumbnail on the left.
组织一系列内容的东西
You have seen the usage of these on many different places on websites.
我想你应该在很多其它地方看到过 类似于这样的排版
For example, if you want to display a list of comments,
比如说 如果你想显示一系列的评论
you could include also the image of the commenters.
你就可以像这样组织 左边放评论者的相片 右边放内容
If you have a list of items being displayed for example, on
如果你想在一部手机上 显示一系列内容
a mobile device, you would often see that there is a thumbnail along the left, and
你大概也能经常看到这样的排版
some description on the right in the list of items being displayed on the screen.
图片在左 内容在右
All of these will benefit from the media-object class.
所有这些排版 都得益于多媒体对象
So exploring further, the media-object class includes the media class,
让我们学习一下怎么实现 多媒体对象的内容部分
which you apply to the outermost div.
首先正如我们学过的 对最外层的 div 设置 class="media"
The media-object class, which you apply to the inner div.
然后在其下放一个设置了 class="media-body" 的 div
The media-body class.
这个 div 下面就是你放内容的地方
Then the media-heading class.
你可以放一个设置了 class="media-heading" 的 h 类标签
The media-heading class is applied to the heading that is
来作为你这块内容的标题
displayed inside the media-body.
为了让排版优雅 如果你要写标题的话 我建议你设置上这个类
Now, positioning of the image is controlled by using
接着是控制图片在左在右的问题 你可以通过两个类来控制
the media-left and the media-right classes.
分别是 media-left 和 media-right
The media-right div,
如果你用了 media-right
if you are using, should always be placed after the media-body div.
那么这个放图像的 div 就要放在 你的主内容 div 的下面
Media-left div as you saw in the example, is placed before the media-body div.
如果是像之前那个栗子里那样用 media-left 就需要把这块 div 放在主内容 div 之前
The media objects can also be included inside lists,
如果你想把多媒体对象放在一个列表里面
by using a ul media-list class being applied to it.
你就需要对 ul 标签设置上 class="media-list"
So, this would be one way that you can display a list of comments
举回刚刚的栗子 如果你要显示一系列的评论
on your website.
你就可以通过一个设置了 class="media-list" 的列表来实现
You can also use another class called a responsive embed for
如果你想在你网站中嵌入某些内容
embedding content on your websites.
你就可以使用 embed-responsive 类
We have seen when you embed content, like videos on your website,
我们的课程视频就是很好的 嵌入内容的栗子
you would use tags like embed or iframe or video tags there.
你可能会用到诸如 iframe 标签 和 embed-responsive-item 等东西
Now, any one of these can be embellished using the Bootstraps embed-responsive tag.
有了它们 你就能把很多东西 嵌入到你的网站中了
And then together with embed-responsive-16by9,
通过应用 embed-responsive-16by9
or embed-responsive-4by3,
或者 embed-responsive-4by3
to specify the size of the embedded object being displayed.
你甚至能定制嵌入对象的格式
The embedded object itself carries the embed responsive item class there.
不过若如此 则不要忘记为你的嵌入对象 设置上 class="embed-responsive-item"
So, embedding media content on your webpage and making it responsive,
总之如果你想嵌入一个
means that you apply the embed-responsive-item
响应式的多媒体内容时
class to either the embed iframe, video, or object tags.
你就要为相应的标签 设置上 class="embed-responsive-item"
You enclose that inside a div.
然后要把这些内容封装进一个 div 中
And for the div, you apply the embed-responsive and embed-responsive-4by3
对于这个 div 你需要设置 class= "embed-responsive embed-responseive-4by3"
or embed-responsive-16by9 to the embed div itself.
当然把 -4by3 改成 -16by9 也行
We'll now move to our next exercise, which examines images and media.
接下来 我们将进行一个练习
So in this exercise,
来进一步学习和巩固 图像和多媒体的各种知识
we're going to use the Bootstrap classes to embed a sponsored image on our website.
我们将会应用 Bootstrap 类来嵌入一个图像
We'll also use the media-object class to include images on description
我们还会实现一个多媒体对象 这个多媒体对象会包含一个
on our website.
有描述内容的图像 【翻译 - Carefree0910】